Contact

hwang.pink@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/han-tran-5b6746164 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Public Speaking Strategic Planning Presentations

Languages

Korean (Elementary)
English (Professional Working)
Vietnamese (Native or Bilingual)

Han Tran

Stars can't shine without darkness

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

I am a junior student at HUFLIT University majors in Business English. I have experience in studying abroad and I strengthen my skills in education field since I got a full scholarship to Europe in 2018. I can describe myself as a young, dynamic, self-motivated to study and work simultaneously. In the long-term, I want to be a person who is an expert in Education field. Please contact me if you have any opportunity, I am willing to learn and share my knowledge.

Experience

CB Centres
IELTS Assistant
August 2022 - September 2022 (2 months)
Ben Tre, Vietnam

du hoc Khanh Nguyen Translator July 2022 - August 2022 (2 months) Remote

Portico & Bridge
Telesales
April 2022 - May 2022 (2 months)
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

- -Contacting potential or existing customers to inform them about immigration programs (Australia, Canada, USA, Europe) using scripts
- -Asking questions to understand customer requirements and close sales

WOW Law Group Legal Intern February 2021 - March 2021 (2 months) Garden Grove, California, United States

- -Field: Personal Injury Law
- -Draft documents and perform complex legal research using research tools

- -Prepare and organize files
- -Do a summary and identify each case

Freelance

English Tutor October 2017 - November 2017 (2 months)

- -Provide useful resources for students to learn English
- -Teaching IELTS for adults

Education

HUFLIT

Bachelor's degree, English Language and Literature/Letters · (September 2020 - 2024)

University of Pécs

Bachelor's degree, International Relations and Affairs · (2018 - 2021)

UNIVERSITY OF SOCIAL SCIENCES AND HUMANITIES (USSH)

Bachelor, International Relations and Affairs · (September 2017 - 2018)

Nguyen Thi Minh Khai High School for the gifted High School Diploma, English · (September 2014 - May 2017)